<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Hair By Iwona - Clitheroe]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Hair By Iwona - Clitheroe]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/hair-by-iwona/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 May 2016 17:05:21 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/hair-by-iwona/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>The Clitheroe Advertiser and Times has teamed up with the Ladies Room to offer one lucky reader a VIP experience at the highly anticipated opening ceremony of the new salon on 3 October.</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/hair-by-iwona/the-clitheroe-advertiser-and-times-has-teamed-up-with-the-la/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">e3c6be38-d60e-419a-a30e-6b1fcbc1b6d2</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2016 17:05:19 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/9fbe8288-b89a-44fc-8784-e2c7f6ac9ef5.jpg" alt="" title="">]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/hair-by-iwona/if-you-recommend-one-of-your-friends-to-me-i-would-have-the/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">894336ec-421c-4308-ba74-01c584fc342c</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2016 17:01:19 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/78a262fe-21b1-4c79-8599-f6662286e679.jpg">]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/hair-by-iwona/3fb01f8d-3ff5-495b-a84b-33081ca67f38/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">3fb01f8d-3ff5-495b-a84b-33081ca67f38</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2016 17:00:45 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>The grand opening of the highly anticipated new salon, The Ladies Room in Clitheroe was a remarkable success, on Saturday as reams of people stopped by to see the latest place to get their locks chopped.Winner of a VIP competition Caroline Edmondson also received an exclusive tour of the hairdressers with a drinks reception and complimentary treatment before the salon was officially opened to the public.Once Caroline was acquainted with the salon, owner Iwona Dahar welcomed local visitors for the official unveiling and spent some time getting to know potential future clients.Iwona has more than 20 years experience in the styling industry and was a renowned hairdresser in the South before relocating to the North West, following her investment in her new Clitheroe-based salon.With two decades worth of experience and knowledge, Iwona will bring Ribble Valley residents the very best in hair care and style.Competition winner Caroline had a firsthand view of Iwona’s stunning new salon and has won a complimentary cut and blow.Caroline said: “Iwona was so welcoming and the salon looks great. I was so pleased to have won the competition and I wish her the best in her new business venture, I am sure she will find incredible success.”Iwona said: “The opening was fantastic, there is a great buzz about the salon and it was great to meet some new people. Clitheroe is such a fantastic place to live. Having recently moved here I have been overwhelmed by how friendly everyone is and I cannot wait to get to know my clients better.”</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/hair-by-iwona/the-grand-opening-of-the-highly-anticipated-new-salon-the-l/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">68e71573-bdf1-4d8d-8231-2362b5c1b989</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2016 16:58:24 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Dear Clients,Very exciting news!</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/hair-by-iwona/dear-clients-very-exciting-news/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">1e6b7550-39d2-4b24-9c37-ac3c60cbfe05</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2016 16:43:08 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>